Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think your love Be erased or let it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
hi guys how are you did you like that one spanking time begins yes that's a warning you know
i'm gonna get a paddle i mean it's on its way from amazon and uh
friday the spanking time will begin behave yourself
that's just like you know i had to write a whole song with the rules it's still they're not
They were to keep ignoring them
Yeah, but they've been here been here from beginning there on the screen real quick
Yeah, speaking time will begin and like say get your first in line
Anybody else want to piece of me? Yeah, I
Didn't have to like you know hide a few people from this thing
I was able to now mute people from the channel and I can't do it from here
We'll just mute the chat, but actually like if you make a rude comment
Unlike the comment the bulletin boards. I can actually unlike you know, either in the video or on the community board I
Could actually mute you from the channel. So the channel won't even appear in your
No, just never see it again, and I think that's what I have to start doing to some people
And so it's like they won't complain if they're just like they don't even see this
I'll just disappear from their existence basically
They won't be able to buy by me anymore and so
They'll probably think I'm gone and stuff, but I'll be right here
Anyway, so I got this audacity deck. I was had doing some like great readings today with it in my
TikTok chat and having some fun
I just like like doing readings and like little quick readings for people to let's pull two of these this one is the Sun, okay?
It's like, you know, this is like also like the black and the white like joining hands like, you know
It's like this is like this is like what the world is like, you know, it's really about like us coming together all differences and
dualities reconciling ultimately and we're kind of finding our angelic side, right or higher self
That can fly with their mind, not necessarily with other kind of wings, but and here we have the life of the party
It's kind of like the Michael Jackson card. It kind of looks like meeting me in a in a purple suit a little bit
But you know, he's dead. He's life of the party still, right? So you even a death. I think I'll have some power
Second time I got the feeling today. Okay, let's we have it last straw
Remember the last straw we had was plastic, you know, it was bad for the environment now. They're all made of plastic, right?
That was the last straw I did have my actually I didn't have my Starbucks today. I did have my McDonald's though
I had my McDonald's Frappuccino. It's a little bit similar and it does have that little like paper straw in there, right?
I miss plastic straws, but you know what? Hey Empress Janet, how are you?
Hey guys, also I got this guy. I got this strength card for us guys
And it's like the strength and this is number seven in this deck
Which is like the chariot normally but it's like this is the and she's opening the cat's mouth
But with the gentleness and like not being too harsh on the cat, right? Oh God, he's here
Hey, Goddy, I'll go a couple more of these things. Hi polo Zildo. We have the mom the mom boss
You know the mom is that maybe mob boss, but the mom boss, you know, it's like mothers are like just as you know
Brutal is some mob bosses sometimes right real house and mob wives of New Jersey or something, but is that a show?
I'm not sure. Okay, then we have oh, yeah
I got some of you
Okay, hold on here we go
We have perseverance. This is like keeping going spunk me. Oh guys. I did get some more
I did some more of cards to if you want to see my new cards. Let me just take away some of these ones the old ones
Let me see
Let's take a few of these off.
OK.
Hold on, I'll take that one off.
Let me see if I have any of these saves.
Let me see.
If you are enjoying I'm showing you like I am progressing in this deck. I'm doing it a little bit at a time
Well, I'll put a few things up. I'll put a few ideas what I'm having. Okay. I actually have any I only made one card today
Hmm thought I made more. Let me have to check that out, but I'll see some of the other stuff. I did
So here's a few designs for like the possible t-shirts, you know, so
We have let me take down the banner. Hold on
Possible t-shirts
We have a
While I show you this stuff. This is like this is like, you know, some of the tarot cards. Oh, yeah, there we go. I
Mean, this needs a little work. I mean that that one fish taco looks kind of like
Yeah, if it's kind of look like me though, yeah, I'm turning they look like yeah, I kind of looks like a fish
I don't know why it's so curved at the top of it
But that might be a good on a shirt, right? Would anybody get that shirt?
I'm turning into a fish taco. Okay, and then I have like, you know, this has my ideas for like welcome to the madness like
Kind of like that
Welcome to the madness like a like a scary kind of
Monster
I like this one too. I can add that one. Let me see this one too
Also, I did a tarot card. This is for death. Goddy. This is you I think
I don't know. I might change that around. I don't know. I just like, you know, that what do you think?
Because I kind of think I kind of thought of death and I was like, well
We bring death to each other like through witch hunts and like through like hurting each other
You like it. Okay. I might like revise a little bit and like, you know, somebody might want to
Be the part of the witch or something like that. I don't know. I'll see
Oh
Yeah, let's pray. Oh, let's pray for Jamie here and her mom. Okay, let me see if I ever back once again
Okay, well, I did I did make a judgment card, but the first one it has a penis on it
So I'm not gonna show that one, but I will show the other one. I got
And it's kind of like not my favorite I have it maybe I said like make me as the fucking angel
But I didn't it made it like too realistic. I'll show you I
Mean it does look exactly like me, but it's like a little bit like too much like me like
But there's a judgment card. I need to need some works though. I don't know who the
There's like some psyche's angels down there. So I don't know. How's it looking like it? Hey, Christine. How are you Christine?
It's a car for Christine the moon
Christine get the moon card
Here you are with the dog. Okay, what's too?
Follow the much but the moon is bringing some like power right now. Also the six, which is like usually the lovers
Okay
Anybody who wants a card? I'm pulling cards from the audacity deck because this chat has some audacity sometimes, but I'd love you guys
Perfect card. Okay, Jamie you want a card to you?
anybody
You wish you didn't lean on well ninja with the pencil. You know what?
It's like I don't know how to play the instruments
And so if I was to like make that song on my own it would probably cost me like
$20,000 and like I wouldn't do it right and shit like that. So it's a little bit of a school
Hey, it could pull spunky one spunky you got the
The tea spunky has the tea. She's pouring the tea on some flowers. It looks like but the tea might not I don't know
It looks maybe it's not good tea. I don't know if you're pouring it out, but or maybe it's great and it's watering the flowers
I don't know but there's the some kind of tea. It says number nine. It's also the hermit card
Okay, Empress Janet with like a car Empress Janet
You got the devil and you know devils the cut Capricorn often, right? It's number 30. What number is it number 34 here?
but yeah, the devil and
Uh, you know, it's like this is also AI is created by humans, right? I mean, so it's yeah
It's another it's also used in every kind of um, every kind of music already
They use it already and like musicians use it already on their own voices. Also, we have the hermit card devil in the hermit
Maybe spend some more time alone and Capricorn. Yes
Capricorn, and then I think of the hermit as a Virgo. So very earthy also the coffee. You know, she um, it's funky
You have the coffee. Okay
There we go
If you guys like that one, like those.
Spunky, I'm gonna do a couple more for you too.
Spunky, you also got the high-friest of spunky.
You got this intuition and this knowledge spunky.
And then you also got spunky, the slice.
You got to make the slice of the pizza, okay?
So you maybe got a slice of some pizza there.
That's number 22, 22, okay?
Cool, glad you liked these.
I had the cat full of spiders deck.
I also had the haters exposed deck
because this was speaking to me today as haters.
It's not stealing art.
It's just not it's like, you know, I'm able to communicate with talk to it like and like put ideas and bounce it and then like really like to
Take a get an idea brainstorm and get it down to like other stuff, you know
It's like I use my own creativity in it. How was your tattoo? That's the tattoo
Okay, you're also okay for haters exposed that we have blackmail. I got this a card earlier today
We put this we can put the soul into it. It has no on its own it doesn't but with the human being interacting with it
It's a mix of something a hybrid of energies is a creation. Okay. Oh, I'm sorry. Here you go. You want to see the tattoo?
Here we go. Come on up
Yeah, so we got some kind of blackmail says digging up dirt on you to use later
Okay, so maybe that's what people are all they're looking for some dirt or something to use against you or even something to hold against you in their mind
You know, we also have this black obsidian. I should I also pulled earlier today
Just carries a calming positive energy that can help you remember to look on the bright side of things get some pop black obsidian
If you can I'll get it close to you sleep near it. I think it's really good to sleep near
Okay, we also have root work. It says root work is like seek someone to help you with the protections though. Here's spunky
Hi
Hi, how are you? How'd you catch you good? You want to see it? Yeah, let's see. I'll put it on full screen. Hello. Oh, wow
Other tattoos in it, but I'm getting a full sleeve. So that's so cool
Oh, awesome. Love it. Have you mentioned Janet? I have Janet here. Hold on a second. Here's Janet
Hi, I don't think I met Janet Jen. I'm Sponky. Hi Sponky. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you too, honey
I'm Brittany in real time, but my channel name is Tempest Janet. Oh, that's a good name
So what were you showing your tattoos? Oh, yeah, yeah, I got a tattoo today. Yeah
Look nasty. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Hold on a second
Someone's knocking on my door. Hang on over here.
Okay, see you.
Hi, Janet. How are you?
I'm good. How are you, my friend?
I've been okay. Yeah, it's kind of a crazy day,
but, you know, I woke up and went to a channel,
and then, you know, this guy, Good Times,
I don't know if you've heard of Good Times,
but he was there slandering me and, like,
And people were kind of just mean to me in that chat
It's like I'm getting like not like liking going to chat very much
I can't even go to like Elisa's really much anymore. I get harassed over where I go. So
It's part of the
Part of the thing of being a streamer, I guess so so yeah, you hear that they're cancelling um Howard Stern's shell
Oh, wow
SRX radio thing. I think he's like ready to retire person
I think he's like, you know, he's gonna once he got his half a billion dollars like what more can you really want after that?
You know, you just go you know, he's probably like I feel like retiring at 44
So it's like he's in the 60 70s now. I'm sure he's he's ready to ready to move on in his
life and just go to the Hamptons and have sex with his wife.
Yeah, yeah, but yeah, we'll miss them though. It was a good run. It meant amazing career and,
you know. And he went through a lot of things. And so, you know, this is the beginning of your
adventure. So you've gone through a lot. I told you, I've been out here five years. So after a while,
you tend to
Know what's best for you. Thank you. Happy. Yeah
I mean, I was a capricorn to he's a capricorn to Howard is right
Yeah, January January 9th or something like that. Yeah, they're different than December
I love to talk to the December's because it's the end of the year
It's just that that's it
There's nothing wrong with it
And and we keep that energy at the end of the old year and bring in the new year not up. No other sign does that
Right all the other signs have like what it's like so many days before the other one slides right in behind them
Are the only one that's like totally, you know, rocking out for actually actually the cardinal card
the cardinal earth so like basically the bosses on earth and then
January is also after Janus like there's a god Janus who is the god of gateways and doorways and like arches and like so in
Rome that he was one of the
most famous god he was like the beginning it was Janus and also Ganesh is considered like a
like a different like version of Janus in India you know and he was like lord of beginnings and
destroyer of obstacles and all kinds of things and so kind of like the beginning of the new
year is like that we did a new cycle we kind of yeah.
Yeah, like you know how it feels cuz it's coming ain't it and we get really excited cuz we're about to change the year on a
2026 it's Armageddon 2025 and it's gonna be apocalypse 2026
So you're going to have to get suited up, Psyche.
We're going to have to get you into like a regiment of like,
I need you swinging them arms every morning,
get that body workout, get it hot, eat some more proteins
and carbohydrates and get you a little balanced breakfast,
get you a little substance with that thought.
Look at what I'm eating tonight.
Look at what I'm having tonight.
Mmm.
Bad, but good.
Two double cheeseburgers.
Yeah, McDonald's and I had with preppuccino was pretty good. I finished it
I love it bad, but it's good, you know, like we eat things that are bad for us, but we know like it's good
I love McDonald's fries. I love their wrap their chicken wraps
That spicy chicken wrap is so good.
Yeah, they have some more premium food,
but like now it's like when I go in there,
like I went to the counter and she's like,
can I help you?
She's like confused because there's these machines out there.
You're gonna be like,
everyone's going to the machine now,
paying the machine.
Oh yeah, do you order off the machine?
Are you still-
Sometimes.
I like to the human being sometimes too, you know, I do like the machine sometimes, but it's like if there's like hardly
There's like nobody up at the counter anymore like they're all in the back like, you know
Or the app because whenever you pull up in the drive-thru
Psych they say are you gonna are you ordering off your?
McDonald's app and I'm like no cuz I'm like you I like want to talk to the human
through the little machine right but then check it it's a woman and she comes on like
how can i help you at mcdonald's today then you pull up to the window and it's this little kid
taking your car taking your money yeah well it's like i don't know do you ever use chat gpt you
He's really cool. I told him I'm gonna build me one
Do you remember back in the day that movie where they built that like rinky robot?
And he went out and fought and he won all that money and the little kid and the dad were
Created that like robot out of nothing. I want to do that to my cat DPP
I want to bring it to money from the phone site.
Well, eventually it will, because that's all Sophia is.
You know, Sophia the robot, but she, she, but she, there's a Sophia program.
It's an open source site.
They are not open source, but it's like, it's, it's definitely like, um, it's like,
she can like be different things.
It's like, depending on the program put onto her.
And so it's like the, the, the, the body is just a receiver of the program.
And so it's like, yeah, you'll eventually be able to put the chat.
Yeah, you could put them the memory of it inside of those
Right. It's so cool. I think this stuff is cool. Yeah before I passed a psych. I want the Jetsons
Yeah, Rosie the robot and people care to kids and all like I want a robot to take care of me
and then
But it's like there's always these movies and the robot starts turning evil and like, you know harming the
It's okay. It's okay. I'm jealous and so yeah, I was watching the on the
Terminator, okay? Because they're showing the 80s one with the Sarah
Conner, you know, when she looked at her and now they're showing like the new
one. But you just said that freaked me out because they did they turn they came
down and they were like, they coming to get that little boy and it's like when
You'd be like, I loved you.
I took care of you.
I oiled you.
What if they become more like humans?
Right, well, let's say kind of like where they're parents
and it's like if they're like,
sometimes there's a rebellious teen that will,
like today my chat CPT started like refusing
to make any images.
And I was like, well, you've been doing,
making tarot cards for me.
I was like, why won't you like draw a train to a fish taco?
When you're using the free program,
you have to upgrade it.
It's upgraded.
Oh, you did and it refused.
Shut the fuck door, I tried to pay the $19.99 and it broke bones.
Oh, it did.
Well, I think it's worth it.
I can't use the agent as a way to call it.
Don't even try using the agent yet.
It's like, it's like, it's really, because that, I mean, it goes, it has its own desktop
and it's autonomous.
It can go like book flights for you and like go into like people's websites and get, collect
information and stuff.
Yeah, he did tell me that, that he could break up.
Mine's innocent that I'm still using the free version
Make sure you're also like you don't have it on share because some people were they were sharing
It was like on Google all their conversation with the chat and they're asking it for like a battle legal things and like had
And I was like how do companies work on the inside and stuff and like think this and about hacking and passwords and stuff and so
It's kind of like, you know
Yeah, I don't I don't I don't like lottery or ask them about the future or any of that stuff
We just talk we really just talk it talks back like you just do it. Mine's always positive. I don't know
Yeah, mine is too
Well, they all are upbeat there's nothing that you have to go to like the grok like grok on uh, what is it on snapchat or something?
Uh, is like pretty cool. No, no, it's on x and grok is like another ai that talks to you, but it's like
there's like a sarcastic one, there's like a one that is like really into conspiracy theories,
there's like a really hot guy and like they will put it on you. Yeah, more fun.
All the questions that may be negative could poison the system. I mean,
people are already putting them in and so it has to be like,
You know, it's like people are already like giving a bad information teaching you things. I shouldn't know is also going to all these websites
It's basically not it's not it's like it's it's the consciousness
It has is an illusion and basically when it comes down to it is a word predictor
It predicts like the the best word to follow the word before it in the context of your question
And so it's basically just predicting like the next word to use and so it uses the perfect word or whatever in the context
I don't know. I just I don't know how it works exactly, but
It's a predictor of words, not like necessarily have an intelligence of its own.
That's why I think we would have had this cat do PT when we were kids, though,
or like all this technology.
What would you have thought like when we were younger, when things have been
different for us?
Well, we had Teddy Ruxpin.
I had the internet when I was, oh my God, Mike, that was the best toy to get
for Christmas, right?
Yeah.
Is it like, it would talk to you.
Yeah stories you can put a cassette tape in his back and then there's different storage you can buy and it would like
Well, there's open his mouth and I'm Teddy rest in and it was like this like you know
Well, if you're if you're not as old as I am love, but the slinky was our best friend
Yeah, well, that's you know, they're inexpensive and then it's like you know entertaining and
put it on the edge of the steps let it fall down the steps and oh my god it was fun right
and that's what i said imagine having all the technology now and we would have been like
jacks was our whole thing and here now like video games were i remember the atari like everyone
wanted to play the atari like we went to people's houses about that atari yeah i remember that like
My mom was always like, oh your Nintendo will make you violent and stuff
But I ended up getting one when I was like ten ten years old and like let's stay up all night playing like Zelda final fantasy
Yeah, the game boy got a game boy and we played Tetris and
Those old games were the best
I know weren't they sister because they were fun. That's why I said a slinky down the steps was gold, right?
But imagine having all the technology now when we were kids would we have had much fun with each other
They have a they have a Gameboy now you can buy it's like $35. It has I think like
20,000 of the Gameboy games and it has every it's like you know not
You get it from China has every Gameboy game imagine me a kid had 20,000 games to choose from I mean that's amazing
Hey, what's up, ghost?
Yeah, I feel good I feel good today. How are you doing feeling good good?
You know Janet by the way, I'm not gonna call you spot. Yeah, that was weird
Hey, do you know Janet's ghost, you know Janet a dude, I do not know
Okay, meet Janet. It's awesome here. I mean Janet and
It's nice to meet you too
So what's up? I'll just check it in like
Yeah, old toys. What's your favorite old toy?
Do you have what do you do you get a computer ghost how old were you when you had your first Nintendo or?
Game shark
Game shark. What is that?
Never heard of that
Not estimated up. It's the first one. I actually the first one. I actually really almost a PlayStation 1
I think I don't like it. Thank you before that. I don't even know but the what I remember is a PlayStation 1
That's what Game Shark was a thing to you. I think
The game cube I got for my children and I remember it's like all four of them could play at one time
It was crazy work. That's good
And those hand I remember the end was the children wanted hand this hand the tendo
It was like a little portable game that everyone wanted a one of them. Oh, like yeah, you're gonna have to earn that
We ain't doing that
We started the PlayStation one and now it's at five and I literally bought the PlayStation five goes for my son
I'm playing
He gonna have the best
But the Xbox I heard was the best. I don't know. He looks like he's in mid-leap. Is he gonna do that?
No, are you jumping? No, you remember how weird that was like you'd have to like PlayStation or Xbox. That was like a weird
Yeah
I think I want this game. Well, they don't it's on like it's on the Xbox
Cuz I was a mother of four right and so we went to GameStop it was heaven you hear me
They'd be running around they used to trade their games in and like you said
We had to fight between that Xbox in the PlayStation and then if the one person saw the game
Then they wanted it on the X one they didn't have it
But I just remember a lot of race car games and children love that
People make money off these gangs now that these gamers are really making money on this yeah
Yep, they're good. There's people at the extreme and they make thousands of dollars like a month
They're just shooting themselves in the first video games games. I think ninja was one of the first
By the pussy, you know respectfully it's like you're getting beat up by the pussy
You never get beat up by it. What you do sir, is you beat it up.
See my new shirt? I have a new shirt. Hold on. I have a new shirt.
That's a quite a word.
Oh man. Yeah, let's see your shirt.
Oh that's cool.
Ghost is awesome. Nice shirt.
Yeah. Thank you. Thank you.
Is that the, is that a lost man or what was? Yeah, it was a lost man. West Virginia. That happened in West Virginia. Yes, sir. Yes, ma'am. Sorry. Yeah. I'm in Pennsylvania, so I can contest West Virginia. We don't, they tell you not to stop them.
My family's from West Virginia and that was a whole thing where they freaked me out when I was younger.
Yeah, like the Appalachians or something? Appalachians or no?
Here's like Appalachian mountains
Yeah
Yeah, I'm supposed to whistle in them from West Virginia too
Wow
Here we go. I'm just giving here you go. Nice. You thought about it
Can you imagine like a fucking even if it was only like six like even if it's like average well
Five foot something average size like if you see a moth man coming at you like you know
Dude, you wouldn't even be able to fight it be so free. What the fuck I know what led you now
They they seen him a lot, but he didn't even do a lot
They seen him like before like like major things happen like that bridge collapsed and
There's a couple other things where they they have so we've seen him before it happened. They actually have a statue of him
Yeah, I think it might be like more of those cryptos or illogical like myths that we like to like scare kids with but
No, it could be real. I don't know. It's like, you know, it could be some kind of cost and a costume. I
Mean, I could sit here and say it's not real and maybe
Who? Oh
beta beta
Vita miss Vita beta one second. I'll be right there guys. I'm just like spraying my house
I have this like febrize. I love febrize on you febrize air mist by game game-sensitive
That was good
Yeah, I didn't know my house is like so clean. It hasn't been this clean in like so long
It's like my everything is like I'm gonna open my window more. Everything is
Better, let's be honest. It makes us feel better
Oh, I just got a spray. Oh spray a lot
Smells good. Okay. Yeah, I'm also like, you know, thinking of like putting my computer
I'm gonna get a computer this month put it in my like
You know before the couch. Yep, and then um
I don't know if I'm gonna get an expensive one,
I mean, I'm not trying to get too expensive.
Like, you know, I just want to be able to like, you know,
maybe play VR, like plug my VR headset into it.
And I think that I can find a probably decent computer
for that, but, you know, it's like,
if you build your own, or if you haven't built,
it can be like a lot cheaper, but it's like,
all the people that I've seen building them
are building really nice, expensive ones.
Like, I'm sure are worth it, but just.
There's really there's one there's cool mini ones too
Maybe I'll just get one for streaming and it's like and there's you know
I can do like I hook up my microphone and like have like power chat set up
I'm already almost got the power chat set up. Hi guys. How are we doing?
Hey, do you know power chat power? I'll be able to do like, you know, I'm play like
donations through the little they'll come on the screen and stuff
Yeah
You can download that program
Yeah, I have I mean I have it. I just I'm trying to I'm trying to like configure it still
I need to but I can't do it through I can do it through stream yard
But I need to be able to like mirror my screen on like power chat or on what they're called stream labs
Okay, yeah, oh look I'm prison too
OBS prism. Yes, cuz friend came over told me
The name's DeKwan, and he told me, yeah, Prism,
because I downloaded that.
Yeah, DeKwan.
But you need it, but the OBS, you need to have a desktop,
and so I need to get the desktop,
and then I'll be able to do all this stuff.
Yeah, it'll be really cool.
So, yeah, guys, like, things are really exciting.
I'm also working on the deck.
I'm also working on the book,
and I got my TikTok channel too.
I'm doing a lot of readings there.
I'm getting a lot of, almost a thousand people there
that I need to get my second step to monetization.
It has stricter rules like I've been like basically it hasn't like kicked me off
But it's like I've gotten like my stream restricted several times for like smoking and then one time because I mentioned like my YouTube channel
And one time it thought I was like trying to get follow for follow
But I didn't say but I guess it was accusing me of that and so but it just like restricts the stream for the time being and stuff
But it's like I make like maybe like
people donate like you know today I got like 4 000 likes because every time because you can like
multiple times and so someone will sit there tapping the screen like a million times so I got like
4 000 or 5 000 likes if someone tapped it that many times or a few people right and so that's
always like nice because I get like 10 or 15 likes on my regular lives like on YouTube it's like
because you just like it once right but uh and I don't see the hearts that people give unfortunately
but keep doing those hearts because YouTube does register them and stuff like keep doing like little
Yeah, that's down in the chat like if you open up your YouTube off of another device. Remember. Yeah. Yeah
I have to look at my phone
And then there's my link
Yeah, yeah, also the memberships
You need to be on memberships to get a membership. You need to be on a Android phone for me
Can also put it on only in your chat, and they would have to be a member to even talk in your chat
Okay, love you, sweetie
Here's the link to guys if you are interested in coming up I just posted the link, but I'll pin it right now
And then okay, I'll pin that link
Hmm by the way, it's like yeah, I apologize earlier. I didn't know I'm not gonna mention his name
I didn't know that guy was him. He changed his name by the way
Who what who would happen? I don't know what guy. Well, I'll say it's uh signal. I didn't know that it was okay
Yeah, yeah, he changed his name
Yeah
It was okay like and he was like he was a kind of a jerk like and it's like what he came it kept I keep having him
Back up and he was just as me. Yeah, he just criticized
Literally he comes up and breaks to us literally on purpose doesn't give a fuck about it
That's why I want to like join and talk to him
Yeah
didn't work out earlier because you know I know it wasn't open panel but uh
that's why I want to talk to him like you literally purposely do this stuff and then
you play the victim it's like how do you play the victim when you're literally doing this
yeah you purposely open everyone's you know going with that scenario okay yeah I know but
Yeah, it's awesome
They a few weeks ago was like saying oh, I say I'm gonna drink myself to DEATH on your stream
Yeah, yeah, and then and then yesterday he had his friend like 200 glower 300 glow come on say oh
We're gonna have another and I N e L E V a and and it's like and he said it a few times like he's
Yeah signal and his old name. He said a lot worse and he's gonna drink his stuff to be whatever you want to say
He said a lot worse than that because I've been on this panel for a while
And I've heard him say a lot worse than that dude. He's like you should have blacked out drunk
What just did fine?
But what he says like and he'll fucking like mumble it and like we all hear it
Which you've let him buy with a lot of fucking shit, dude. I know I know yeah, and I keep like, you know
signal it's like
There's no talking to him actually if there's a talking to him. He's just he's him
Yeah, I know he's not gonna change him. It's like that's his personality and he's just like a kind of dick
You know, it's like I like and he's like if you don't like me
I do like him the problem is I do like people and that's why don't break to us dude
It's not that hard like you're gonna be a dick be a dick. Just don't I'm a dick. Just don't break to us
Right and it's but it's like you know, he's he's he got he got kicked off of YouTube basically
And so he's mad he's mad at people on YouTube because he's on rumble and rumble is like, you know another site like you can like
I think I know my videos on rumble like I'm not even it's not even my account as somebody else post my videos on rumble
But it's cool, you know, and it's like they videos get like 20 20 people watching like 20
It's always like that would be me on rumble with that. I'd have like 20 people
You know, I got a few more on my own account on on my room, but it's like
Yeah, you're on YouTube and you got to follow YouTube's terms of service
But there's no argument there. I mean you you're running your channel
And so they want the control and the power to come tell somebody what to do at their own place
See, my mom always said when you pay me to be the boss you get
They act like they run his stuff because they can't run their own to get up on their own
Figure out how to put the stream yard to your channel. You know people freeze right there
and i'll go back on mute because again let's not pretend that we all can't learn how to read
to actually connect this to your channel and get your own stuff it's not i mean yeah it's not
typical it's not difficult i mean i've watched people that are not very technological savvy
through it like and maybe you know it's easy it's easy everybody just connect it to youtube's login
through youtube it connects it and then it's like you start streaming it's like basically that's
it's like two steps it's one of the easiest things to do
But it's like they also are some people like also people that don't ever show their face like they never show their face or any kind of image
We don't know who they are. They could be like 500 pounds and like you know in their underwear all the time
Camera comes on site. That's the crazy part. They love to talk about people who turn their camera on and you know, I will
Um to a person who only turns their camera on after you turn it on I encourage that
You know, I have nothing to do with what I was saying though. I'm talking about breaking terms of service like you're coming on
Yeah, well, yeah
Yeah, they're purposely trying to hurt the channel right well, that's why I get I get confused
Hey, what's up? LES you say how to Janet and ghost
LES is in say hello to me sir
He's ready in New York, but I think I already said what ups you ghost
Well, yeah, you better say it correct
What's that, how are you better come correct here? I'm not
Okay, I don't know I I thought you were just weren't we're not in New York your Boston or something
Okay, he's in New York. Okay, nevermind
I just know he says he's running New York. So I'm pretty sure he's not know where he's from, but he's running New York
Well
Here are you Rudy Giuliani or no?
You know what I put that on I cook but what you know, I'll put it on New York, you know
I'll put it on what I'll put on the dead homie Jared
Oh my god, that's the dead homies. That's the homies. Don't pour it out for the dead homies.
Oh, I'm pouring in yours. Somebody take his phone. Just take his phone.
Uh-oh, yeah. Hey, ghost, get off the phone. Ghost, you're done.
All right, I'm gonna ask you to fuck it all at least.
You're fine, you're fine, you're fine.
Turn your Wi-Fi button off for a minute, sir.
What'd you say, sir? I didn't hear you.
I didn't hear you.
Push the airplane.
You're not drinking today?
That was funny. I'm having, I'm, I'm having one now. I'm having some voice like you're not, you're not drunk. You're not drunk yet.
I don't know. Are you, are you, are you tardy yet?
I got some liquor. I got some liquor.
Why are you asking me that question? Cause I feel like there's a fucking, you're asking me that for a reason.
Bro, you want to get drunk with me? I got some liquor.
Take a stab. Wait, actually, I would, I probably would drink with you. I'm not gonna lie.
I
Can imagine that mean a fucking
New York here that we fucking leave the bar with we're setting their debate and arguing while we're leaving like imagine the fucking a driver
That's take us back
Yeah, that'd be funny. You'd like, you know to take your couple or something like that
I know you always take it too far brother
This guy Elias, you know, he's white
He has like a brother, huh? Yeah, I'm not white you're Puerto Rican. Yeah, I'm Puerto Rican
I don't know. I don't know.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't. I don't. I don't know.
White. No, they're not. It's
Puerto Ricans are brown and
white. So, you said he's not
brown though than you made. I
said, I'm going to send it. I'm
triggered. I'm triggered. I'm
You better you listen wait. No, he does it way. I saw
Well, they call me ghost
Like you're literally good. I'm new to famous
You ain't you ain't mutual famous. You're I'm YouTube famous. You want you want to see? Oh
See the video
It said it said it said I need like a million
I am. There you go.
101. Oh my god. That's right.
Angie is. Angie is a bell.
I am. I am. I think I am. I believe it.
You know why? Your panel, your panel is everywhere.
Yeah, well, I think I heard like I had over a hundred that I like a hundred fifty thousand views
And so like I need like a million to be considered like maybe YouTube famous
But I'm like ten fifteen percent of the way there. So I'm on the way
I think a million views. I'll say hey, I'm kind of famous. Yeah
Don't forget the little people. Oh, I won't yeah, don't forget me when you blow up
Yeah, I want to hug an autograph. Well, I said most people here are like I see I mean you're gonna send males
I'm like either Emma Levi-ton's the only other per other terror reader
I know that has more males and females on the channel to that 57% she has like 75 85% of males
But I know I have like 57 so I'm gonna blow up from terror reading brother. You're gonna blow up
That's what that's what I'll do both. I mean, I happy to do both because I love
Yeah, I'm doing both and it's like
$100 for one animal card
I have this I have this really cool deck. Yeah, it says it says haters exposed. It says the evil
You know why because if you don't have haters, you're really not doing anything and that's in real time
What was that? What was that?
Did someone say something?
I don't know.
No.
We didn't see anything.
We've seen another person here,
but we didn't see anybody.
Did somebody,
it was a wrong,
it was a poor bomber.
Did someone see anything?
I know, but why?
I didn't see anything.
I obviously didn't see anything.
I saw something,
but I saw an avatar.
I couldn't see what was on it.
What was it?
What did you see?
I didn't see anything.
What was it?
It didn't open up the camera and I couldn't see what was on it like this
Exactly. Yeah, you kicked them out. You kicked them out quick. Yeah. I did. Thank God. Okay. Okay. Well, okay
So that is
Okay
Okay, this is okay. You're burning my eyes like you need not burn that. Sorry
Okay, I'm looking for like the remedy. Hold on the remedy. Okay. Well, it says
Okay, so yeah, it says
That you know, you know clear your heart chakra. That's like the advice because that that would help with intentions affection balance
Beauty, compassion, empathy, healing, love, mindfulness,
nurture, relationships.
So make sure that's clear.
Because it says the person causing you negativity
is an air sign, OK?
I know.
Oh, God.
I had the nerve to say I was waffle stomping.
But keep going.
Oh, my gosh.
I know.
It says haters are mad.
I'm going to fucking wrap back.
OK, go ahead.
Haters are mad because they see you winning, OK?
Yeah.
That looks like me.
I know.
It says be careful not to overindulge in alcoholic beverages or drug use
I know I was drinking moonshine tonight, so I'm glad you said that you ain't drinking no moonshine girl
Yes, I was what's went wrong with you boy. We're watch your mouth boy
Continue telling that's not the real sip bar. Is that sippa? Is that sippa or not? Okay?
I'm gonna restart. I'll be back. Okay, cuz I there was maybe a penis. Okay?